(Sheldon:)to send the ring back to you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, let's not be hasty.
(Mrs Cooper:)Are you sure it's over for good?
(Sheldon:)It's over for me.
I'm done with women.
(Sheldon:)Like when I swore off Pop Rocks.
(Sheldon:)They both hurt you on purpose.
(Mrs Cooper:)You want to tell me
what happened?
(Sheldon:)Are you going to say
it's all part of God's plan?
(Mrs Cooper:)Good chance.
(Sheldon:)Then no, thank you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, honey,
don't send it back yet.
(Mrs Cooper:)Your sister's married,
and I'm not letting your brother
(Mrs Cooper:)give my grandmother's ring
to that whore he's dating.
(Sheldon:)Wasn't Mary Magdalene
a woman of ill repute?
(Mrs Cooper:)When your idiot brother
redeems mankind,
(Mrs Cooper:)he can date whoever he wants.
(Bernadette:)I know it hurts now,
but it's gonna get better.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Howard:)Everything's gonna be okay.
(Stuart:)You've got so
much to offer.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Stuart:)Any man would be
lucky to have you.
(Bernadette:)That's true.
(Amy:)I just hope
I did the right thing.
(Stuart:)I'm sure you did.
(Stuart:)Maybe that's the problem...
you always do the right thing.